munkyourself.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy

This website is operated by Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment LLC ("Fox"), part of the News America Group, which has adopted a set of Privacy Principles applicable to all its U.S.-based companies. Fox has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use and share personally identifiable information ("PII") we obtain from and about individuals located in the U.S both online and offline.

From time to time Fox may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our web sites, or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of the Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If Fox materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change.

**_ COLLECTION:_** _COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ("PII") BY FOX_

General. Fox collects personally identifiable information ("PII", that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address, credit card information or telephone number) in order to provide you with a requested service or to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats, bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties. 

Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that the Internet sites operated by Fox place on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on our site and enable Fox to make your visits to our site more enjoyable. For example, cookies can track the things you have placed your "shopping cart" during a visit to our online store. Information about your activities on Fox’s site(s) and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.

Third party advertisements displayed on Fox's site(s) may also contain cookies set by Internet Advertising companies or advertisers. Fox does not control these cookies and visitors to our web site(s) sent by Internet Advertisers or other companies should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. Fox may allow third party pixel tags to be present on Fox sites for purpose of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection. We also may use pixel tags in order to recognize users and assess traffic patterns, and we may include pixel tags and cookies in our e-mail messages in order to count how many e-mail messages have been opened.

Fox may use cookies, pixels or similar tools to relate your use of our web site(s) to PII obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to send you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream information about your activities on Fox's website(s) may allow us to limit the materials we send you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. However, if Fox wishes to combine your personal and cookie or clickstream information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent (i.e., "opt in").

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies you won't be able to conduct transactions such as placing an order via our shopping cart or completing a sale for any VHS or DVD merchandise.

**_ NOTICE:_** _FOX WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES_

When you voluntarily provide PII to Fox, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses Fox will make of the information. At the time you provide PII, Fox will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII, including whether we will share it with outside companies (See "Choice" below).

This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and therefore want to share your personal information provided you have given Fox permission to do so (See "Use" below).

Sometimes we collect personally identifiable information from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us.

Fox's web site(s) may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a Fox logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by Fox. Fox's web site(s) may also carry advertisements from other companies. Fox is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site(s) or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet Advertising companies. Once you've left a Fox site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

Fox's web site(s) may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with Fox (i.e., that are part of the News America Group). Although News America Group entities adhere to the Group's Privacy Principles, visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.

**_ CHOICE:_** _FOX WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII_

Fox will not use the PII you provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with Fox (i.e, not part of the News America Group), except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy or unless we obtain your permission. 

**_ USE:_** _FOX'S USE OF PII_

Fox will use your PII in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If Fox obtains PII from a third party such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this policy.

Fox may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us, that is are part of the News America Group of companies. Provided you have given us consent, Fox may also share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with Fox, but would like to send you information about their products and services. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third parties when PII is collected. 

Fox employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. Fox may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who provide services on our behalf. Examples of such services include without limitation website hosting, ad serving, customer service, product purchase services (including order, fulfillment and payment authorization and processing services), fraud prevention and investigation, data analysis and promotional assistance (including sending communications and creating, administering and operating contests, sweepstakes or other games). Such outside contractors or agents may only use PII to provide Fox with a specific service and not for any other purpose unless specified on the Fox website or on any third party website where you participate in the activity(ies). 

There may be instances when Fox may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of Fox, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to protect against fraud and for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if Fox sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, Fox may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction.

**_ SECURITY:_** _FOX PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII_

Fox uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, Fox uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

**_ ACCESS:_** _HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII_

Visitors to Fox websites may review the PII we maintain about them in our records whenever possible. If you would like to review, correct, or delete this information.

Fox Connect  
C/O Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment Online  
2816 Columbia Street

Torrance, California 90503  
Telephone: (888) 223-4369  
International Callers: (310) 217-4764  
Fax: (888) 443-4369  
Email: [ privacypolicy@foxhome.com](mailto:privacypolicy@foxhome.com)

Unless otherwise indicated by Fox, your usual operator rates apply to all telephone, email, SMS or other communications.

**_ REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE:_** _HOW TO CONTACT FOX ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS_

Fox welcomes any suggestions on how to make this website a better and safer place. If you would like to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy or have privacy issues or complaints regarding this policy, please contact us at:

Fox Connect  
C/O Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment Online  
2816 Columbia Street

Torrance, California 90503  
Telephone: (888) 223-4369  
International Callers: (310) 217-4764  
Fax: (888) 443-4369  
Email: [ privacypolicy@foxhome.com](mailto:privacypolicy@foxhome.com)

Unless otherwise indicated by Fox, your usual operator rates apply to all telephone, email, SMS or other communications.
